ISHAN SRIVASTAVA | REACT DEVELOPER

Bangalore, India | +91 8429006689 | ishan.24sri@gmail.com https://github.com/lshanSrivastava24

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Bringing more than 2.8 years of experience leading website design projects, including gathering user requirements, producing code and enhancing designs. Focused on creating clean, robust code. Achieves compatibility targets while meeting and exceeding customer demands.

CORE COMPETENCIES

✓ HTML & CSS

✓ GIT

Javascript

Material UI

React Hooks

✓ State Management System

Responsive Design

Bootstrap

React JS

Context API

Redux

✓ Performance Optimisation

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Movidu Tech pvt ltd.

React Developer | July, 2021 - Present

Movidu (https://movidu.in/)

- Created company website from scratch.
- Developed movidu mentor dashboard and movidu student dashboard from scratch so that
 we can have a track of their work and they can also have a track of their projects and
 others.

Coincent (https://coincent.ai/)

- Developed coincent admin, coincent mentor and coincent student dashboard from scratch.
- Coincent mentor and student dashboard are developed in a way so that they can see their progress and interact with each other on any kind of queries and many other things.
- Coincent admin dashboard Here admin can go through all the 'mentors' profiles and can manage all the mentors review their works and assign them specific classes.

1stop (https://1stop.ai/)

- Developed 1stop admin, 1stop mentor and 1stop student dashboard from scratch.
- In the 1stop mentor and student dashboard there is a community where students from the same group can interact with each other within the dashboard and for interacting with mentors they have a different section for that and many other useful features for their progress.
- In the 1stop admin dashboard admin can set the calendar for any mentor and also assign tasks to the mentors and other works as well.

Digital Savers

Front end developer Intern | May, 2020 - January, 2021

- Worked on html, css and javascript.
- Worked on two main websites of the organisation.
- Developed the dark and light modes on the website.
- Handled the responsive part of the website.

EDUCATION

2019 - 2022 | Lovely Professional University

Bachelor of Computer Application

- Graduated with a GPA of 7.8.
- CEO, WebNerds organisation under DSA.
- Member, DSA of Lovely Professional University.
- Participation Certificate of Hackathon.
- Conducted more than 2 hackathon in my organisation under DSA.